(Leonard:)- Let's just go to your place.
- Lf he's unhappy, shouldn't we talk to him?
"Shouldn't we talk to him?"
Have you learned nothing in six years?
(Penny(entering apartment):)You doing okay, sweetie?
There's ominous music playing
and there's an afghan over my head.
(Sheldon:)I don't know where you're from, but where
I'm from, that means I'm not doing okay.
- I'm gonna make you some tea.
- Tea is for when I'm upset. I'm not upset.
The university is forcing me
to work with Kripke. I'm outraged.
(Leonard:)So cocoa?
(Sheldon:)Yes, cocoa.
(Sheldon:)Do you have any idea what it's like
to be paired with someone so annoying?
Oh, teacher, me, me.
You see, I did all this great work
and now he's just gonna come and ruin it.
I'm angrier than ever
and filled with despair.